Drink it.
Everybody in Costa Rica had a house
juice. We don't have a house juice, so I
made one up. I'm going to show you what
I put in it. I said bad word.
This is a chirimoya.
So I squash a single single fish. You
know, it's kind of a fruit Ow. I lied,
that's an orange, that's a lemon. This
is easier with two people or animals.
You got to Turn this into a Stop. This
is our squash. Is this squash?
Pronunciate more, bro. Is the light bad
here? We need something in it. How you
say it? Hyperbolina.
Now we got to make some Now we got to
make some juice.
This is a chirimoya. That's a pineapple
or an airplane.
And then a coconut. This is how you work
a chirimoya. Forget the bottle. Now
let's make a juice.
What happened to all our coconut trees?
Need a knife.
Is it good?
Drink it. Nope.
Drink it.
I don't know what everybody else in
Costa Rica makes their house juice out
of. We're just going in the yard and
grab a bunch of stuff, put it in the
blender, and then keep adding stuff
until it tastes good. This one turned
out okay.